scholarship-positions.com 2010-11-29

# Free Scholarships International Scholarships and Financial Aid Positions for College

**Privacy Policy Scholarship-Positions.com**

Scholarship-Positions.com is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our data processing practices and your options regarding the ways in which your personal data is used. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to our processing please contact us at admin@scholarship-positions.com.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Your information may be passed to and used by all Scholarship-Positions.com companies. We will never pass your personal information to anyone else, except where we are required or permitted to do so by law. We may also use and disclose information in aggregate (so that no individual customers are identified) for marketing and strategic development purposes.

Our web site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.
